Guide to the Corcoran Gallery of Art and Corcoran College of Art + Design, Corcoran Gallery of Art public relations and graphics records circa 1942-2009 COR0003.3.RG
Special Collections Research Center, The George Washington University
- Exhibition files, 1944-2009; 1983-2009; Series 11
  - Photojournalism Open House Postcards Spring 2002, Series 11 (Box 120, Folder 52)
  - Photojournalism BFA Preview Postcard, 2002 September; Series 11 (Box 120, Folder 53)
  - BFA Photojournalism Mini Catalog Spring 2002, Series 11 (Box 120, Folder 54)
  - Focus on Photojournalism 2002 Spring Poster, 2002 November; Series 11 (Box 120, Folder 55)
  - Focus on Photojournalism (Adult) Spring 2002, Series 11 (Box 120, Folder 56)
  - Portfolio Day 2002 Brochure, 2002 November; Series 11 (Box 120, Folder 57)
  - Portfolio Day Poster 2002, Series 11 (Box 120, Folder 58)
  - Scholastic Art + Writing Invite 2002, 2002 May; Series 11 (Box 120, Folder 59)
  - Senior Exhibition Invite, 2002; Series 11 (Box 120, Folder 60)
  - 1869 Society / Save the date / Pillbox Paparazzi, 2002 January; Series 11 (Box 120, Folder 61)
  - Stanley Tretick Brochure, 2002; Series 11 (Box 120, Folder 62)
  - Stanley Tretick Exhibit Signage, 2002; Series 11 (Box 120, Folder 63)
  - Stanley Tretick Invite, 2002; Series 11 (Box 120, Folder 64)
  - Stovall Invite Postcard 2002, 2002 January; Series 11 (Box 120, Folder 65)
  - Study Abroad Brochure 2002, Series 11 (Box 120, Folder 66)
  - Today Flyer, 2002 April; Series 11 (Box 120, Folder 67)
  - Today Flyer, 2002 May; Series 11 (Box 120, Folder 68)
  - Visiting Artists Program, 2002 February; Series 11 (Box 120, Folder 69)
  - Visiting Lecture Poster Fall 2002, Series 11 (Box 120, Folder 70)
  - Washington Post Leading Ladies Ad, 2002 April 5; Series 11 (Box 120, Folder 71)
  - Washington Post Summer CE 2002 Ad, Series 11 (Box 120, Folder 72)
  - Sally Mann - Clips, Circa 1998-2004; Series 11 (Box 127, Folder 1)
  - Sally Mann - Originals, Circa 1998-2004; Series 11 (Box 127, Folder 2)
  - Sally Mann - Images, Circa 1998-2004; Series 11 (Box 127, Folder 3)
  - Sally Mann - Background, Circa 1998-2004; Series 11 (Box 127, Folder 4)
  - Sally Mann: What Remains - Press Kit, 2004 June12 - September 6; Series 11 (Box 127, Folder 5)
  - Sally Mann Originals, Circa 1998-2004; Series 11 (Box 127, Folder 6)
  - Sanborn - Press Kit, 2003 November 1 - 2004 January 26; Series 11 (Box 127, Folder 7)
  - Sanborn Originals, Circa 1998-2004; Series 11 (Box 127, Folder 8)
  - Sanborn Images, Circa 1998-2004; Series 11 (Box 127, Folder 9)
  - Sanborn Clips, Circa 1998-2004; Series 11 (Box 127, Folder 10)
  - Sanborn Background, Circa 1998-2004; Series 11 (Box 127, Folder 11)
  - Scholastic 2004 Clips, Series 11 (Box 127, Folder 12)
  - Seward Johnson - Originals, Circa 1998-2004; Series 11 (Box 127, Folder 13)
  - The Art of Reading - Beyond The Frame -- press kit, 2003 September 13; Series 11 (Box 127, Folder 14)
  - Seward Johnson - Clips, Circa 1998-2004; Series 11 (Box 127, Folder 15)
  - Seward Johnson: Images, Circa 1998-2004; Series 11 (Box 127, Folder 16)
  - Shomei Tomatsu: Skin of the Nation, Circa 1998-2004; Series 11 (Box 127, Folder 17)
  - Exhibition Clips Listings, Circa 1998-2004; Series 11 (Box 127, Folder 18)
  - 2005 Senior Thesis Exhibitions, Series 11 (Box 127, Folder 19)
  - World Press Photo Clips, Circa 1998-2004; Series 11 (Box 127, Folder 20)
  - Gee's P. Release, Circa 1998-2004; Series 11 (Box 128, Folder 1)
  - Gee's Background, Circa 1998-2004; Series 11 (Box 128, Folder 2)
  - Gee's Images, Circa 1998-2004; Series 11 (Box 128, Folder 3)
  - Gee's Bend - Clips, Circa 1998-2004; Series 11 (Box 128, Folder 4)
  - Gee's - Printed Mater., Circa 1998-2004; Series 11 (Box 128, Folder 5)
  - Gee's - Press Kit, Circa 1998-2004; Series 11 (Box 128, Folder 6)
  - "Here is New York", Circa 1998-2004; Series 11 (Box 128, Folder 7)
  - Home of the Free Clips, Circa 1998-2004; Series 11 (Box 128, Folder 8)
  - Leiber Press Clippings, Circa 1998-2004; Series 11 (Box 128, Folder 9)
  - Leiber Checklist, Circa 1998-2004; Series 11 (Box 128, Folder 10)
  - Leiber Wall Text, Circa 1998-2004; Series 11 (Box 128, Folder 11)
  - Judith Leeiber - Originals, Circa 1998-2004; Series 11 (Box 128, Folder 12)
  - Leiber - Printed Materials, Circa 1998-2004; Series 11 (Box 128, Folder 13)
  - Leiber Press Release, Circa 1998-2004; Series 11 (Box 128, Folder 14)
  - Leiber Background, Circa 1998-2004; Series 11 (Box 128, Folder 15)
  - Italian Renaissance Maiolica, 2005 July 31; Series 11 (Box 128, Folder 16)
  - Melissa Ichiuju (Clips), Circa 1998-2004; Series 11 (Box 128, Folder 17)
  - Memento Background, Circa 1998-2004; Series 11 (Box 128, Folder 18)
  - Memento Clips, Circa 1998-2004; Series 11 (Box 128, Folder 19)
  - Hasbun Originals, Circa 1998-2004; Series 11 (Box 128, Folder 20)
  - Memento Images, Circa 1998-2004; Series 11 (Box 128, Folder 21)
  - MES, Circa 1998-2004; Series 11 (Box 128, Folder 22)
  - Nature Conservancy - Wall Text - Checklist, Circa 1998-2004; Series 11 (Box 128, Folder 23)
  - Nature Conservancy - Clippings, Circa 1998-2004; Series 11 (Box 128, Folder 24)
  - Film Slides, Circa 1998-2004; Series 11 (Box 128, Folder 25)
  - Nature Conservancy - Press Release, Circa 1998-2004; Series 11 (Box 128, Folder 26)
  - Nature Conservancy - Background, Circa 1998-2004; Series 11 (Box 128, Folder 27)
  - Nature, Circa 1998-2004; Series 11 (Box 128, Folder 28)
  - Randall School, Circa 1998-2004; Series 11 (Box 128, Folder 29)
  - Impressionist Tradition in America, 2003; Series 11 (Box 129, Folder 1)
  - Seward Johnson: Press Release, 2003; Series 11 (Box 129, Folder 2)
  - Seward Johnson: Wall Text, 2003; Series 11 (Box 129, Folder 3)
  - Seward Johnson: Background, 2003; Series 11 (Box 129, Folder 4)
  - Seward Contract, 2003; Series 11 (Box 129, Folder 5)
  - Seward Johnson: Printed Materials, 2003; Series 11 (Box 129, Folder 6)
  - Census 03, 2003; Series 11 (Box 129, Folder 7)
  - Census 03: Originals, 2003; Series 11 (Box 129, Folder 8)
  - Scholastic 2003 - Clips, Series 11 (Box 129, Folder 9)
  - Expressions 2003 Clips, Series 11 (Box 129, Folder 10)
  - Robert Frank: Originals, Circa 2003; Series 11 (Box 129, Folder 11)
  - Robert Frank Clips, 2003; Series 11 (Box 129, Folder 12)
  - [Robert Frank Clips Continued], 2003; Series 11 (Box 129, Folder 13)
  - [Robert Frank Clips Continued], 2003; Series 11 (Box 129, Folder 14)
  - Background Robert Frank, Circa 2003; Series 11 (Box 129, Folder 15)
  - Robert Frank Images, Circa 2003; Series 11 (Box 129, Folder 16)
  - Robert Frank Wall Text (Empty), Circa 2003; Series 11 (Box 129, Folder 17)
  - Robert Frank Checklist, Circa 2003; Series 11 (Box 129, Folder 18)
  - Robert Frank Printed Materials (empty), Circa 2003; Series 11 (Box 129, Folder 19)
  - Robert Frank: Press Release, Circa 2003; Series 11 (Box 129, Folder 20)
  - Eyes of History Clips, Circa 2003; Series 11 (Box 129, Folder 21)
  - Eyes of History - Originals, Circa 2003; Series 11 (Box 129, Folder 22)
  - Ellis - Originals, Circa 2003; Series 11 (Box 129, Folder 23)
  - Ellis - Originals, Circa 2003; Series 11 (Box 129, Folder 24)
  - Hassam Clips, Circa 2003; Series 11 (Box 129, Folder 25)
  - [American Art Museum], 2003 June; Series 11 (Box 129, Folder 26)
  - Hassam - Originals, Circa 2003; Series 11 (Box 129, Folder 27)
  - Joseph Mills: Clips, Circa 2003; Series 11 (Box 129, Folder 28)
  - Joseph Mills: Wall Text (empty), Circa 2003; Series 11 (Box 129, Folder 29)
  - Joseph Mills: Printed Materials, Circa 2003; Series 11 (Box 129, Folder 30)
  - Joseph Mills: Checklist (empty), Circa 2003; Series 11 (Box 129, Folder 31)
  - Joseph Mills: Press Releases, Circa 2003; Series 11 (Box 129, Folder 32)
  - Joseph Mills: Originals, Circa 2003; Series 11 (Box 129, Folder 33)
  - [Whistler His Circle in Venice Press Kit], Circa 2003; Series 11 (Box 129, Folder 34)
  - Whistler Printed Materials, Circa 2003; Series 11 (Box 129, Folder 35)
  - Whistler Background (empty), Circa 2003; Series 11 (Box 129, Folder 36)
  - Whistler - Originals, Circa 2003; Series 11 (Box 129, Folder 37)
  - [Whistler His Circle in Venice], Circa 2003; Series 11 (Box 129, Folder 38)
  - Whistler Clips, Circa 2003; Series 11 (Box 129, Folder 39)
  - Exhibitions-Maiolica, Circa 2005-2007; Series 11 (Box 135, Folder 1)
  - Public Programs, 2004; Series 11 (Box 135, Folder 2)
  - Sargent Labels, Circa 2005-2007; Series 11 (Box 135, Folder 3)
  - Mantel Room, Circa 2005-2007; Series 11 (Box 135, Folder 4)
  - [Loose Exhibits Documents], Circa 2005-2007; Series 11 (Box 135, Folder 5)
  - 1002-10-1A Organizational Chart, Circa 2005-2007; Series 11 (Box 135, Folder 6)
  - Tour Request Form, Circa 2005-2007; Series 11 (Box 135, Folder 7)
  - 1002-17 Publication Audit (Forrms), Circa 2005-2007; Series 11 (Box 135, Folder 8)
  - 1007-20 Member Event Template, Circa 2005-2007; Series 11 (Box 135, Folder 9)
  - 1003-35 Calendar (June Events), Circa 2005-2007; Series 11 (Box 135, Folder 10)
  - 1015 Night+Day Brochure, Circa 2005-2007; Series 11 (Box 135, Folder 11)
  - 1003-38 July Events Calendar, Circa 2005-2007; Series 11 (Box 135, Folder 12)
  - [Loose Reports/Invoices], Circa 2005-2007; Series 11 (Box 135, Folder 13)
  - 1015-08 Night Day, Circa 2005-2007; Series 11 (Box 135, Folder 14)
  - PP Calendar Jan/Feb 07, 2007 January - 2007 February; Series 11 (Box 135, Folder 15)
  - PP Calendar, Circa 2005-2007; Series 11 (Box 135, Folder 16)
  - December/January Public Programs Calendar, Circa 2005-2007; Series 11 (Box 135, Folder 17)
  - Pubilc Programs Nov. Calendar, 2005 November; Series 11 (Box 135, Folder 18)
  - Public Programs November 2006, 2006 November; Series 11 (Box 135, Folder 19)
  - [Public Programs Calendar Jan. 007], 2007 January; Series 11 (Box 135, Folder 20)
  - 1015-13 PP Calendar, Circa 2005-2007; Series 11 (Box 135, Folder 21)
  - Flyers (Templates 06), 2006; Series 11 (Box 135, Folder 22)
  - [Night and Day], 2007; Series 11 (Box 135, Folder 23)
  - 1015-09 Night/Day, Circa 2005-2007; Series 11 (Box 135, Folder 24)
  - 1003-22 Front Desk Event Calendar, Circa 2005-2007; Series 11 (Box 135, Folder 25)
  - 1015-11 May Calendar, Circa 2005-2007; Series 11 (Box 135, Folder 26)
  - 1003-33 May Events Calendar, Circa 2005-2007; Series 11 (Box 135, Folder 27)
  - Calendar Night Day, Circa 2005-2007; Series 11 (Box 135, Folder 28)
  - 1043-09 Aspiring Artists Summer 07, 2007; Series 11 (Box 135, Folder 29)
  - CE-07 Ad Spring, Circa 2005-2007; Series 11 (Box 135, Folder 30)
  - JOA-Teachers Pack, Circa 2005-2007; Series 11 (Box 135, Folder 31)
  - MA NAEA + CAA Ads, Circa 2005-2007; Series 11 (Box 135, Folder 32)
  - 1039-06 NEA Ad, Circa 2005-2007; Series 11 (Box 135, Folder 33)
  - Phil Solomon, Circa 2005-2007; Series 11 (Box 135, Folder 34)
  - 1043-07 Focus Brochure, Circa 2005-2007; Series 11 (Box 135, Folder 35)
  - Entrance Signage, Circa 2005-2007; Series 11 (Box 135, Folder 36)
  - Front Desk, Circa 2005-2007; Series 11 (Box 135, Folder 37)
  - Instiutional Folders, Circa 2005-2007; Series 11 (Box 135, Folder 38)
  - 1006-02 Corporate Funding Insert, Circa 2005-2007; Series 11 (Box 135, Folder 39)
  - [Loose Documents], Circa 2005-2007; Series 11 (Box 135, Folder 40)
  - Annual Report, Circa 2005-2007; Series 11 (Box 135, Folder 41)
  - Chaser PAQ - Drafts, Circa 2005-2007; Series 11 (Box 135, Folder 42)
  - College Catalogue, Circa 2005-2007; Series 11 (Box 135, Folder 43)
  - Library Hours Etc, Circa 2009; Series 11 (Box 145, Folder 1)
  - Art the Book Brochure - 1168-015, Circa 2009; Series 11 (Box 145, Folder 2)
  - Salon Dore Brochure Redesign 1169-008, Circa 2009; Series 11 (Box 145, Folder 3)
  - Expressions 2009 Postcard 1229-001, Series 11 (Box 145, Folder 4)
  - 2009 Senior Thesis 1212, Series 11 (Box 145, Folder 5)
  - 2009 Focus Pre-College Brochures 1121-003, 1121-004, Circa 2009; Series 11 (Box 145, Folder 6)
  - March '09 Night Day 1152-008, 2009 March; Series 11 (Box 145, Folder 7)
  - April '09 Night Day 1168-009, 2009 April; Series 11 (Box 145, Folder 8)
  - On View Spring 2009 1155-003, Series 11 (Box 145, Folder 9)
  - February '09 Night Day 1152-007, 2009 February; Series 11 (Box 145, Folder 10)
  - A Love of Europe Exhibitions, 2009; Series 11 (Box 145, Folder 11)
  - Sargent and the Sea Exhibition 1087, 2009; Series 11 (Box 145, Folder 12)
  - Sargent Exhibit Proposal (1087-13), 2009; Series 11 (Box 145, Folder 13)
  - Recent Acquisitions 1169-032, 2009; Series 11 (Box 145, Folder 14)
  - Maya Lin - Systematic Landscapes 1151, 2009; Series 11 (Box 145, Folder 15)
  - Eggleston Exhibition 1194, 2009; Series 11 (Box 145, Folder 16)
  - Eggleston MPN Invite, 2009; Series 11 (Box 145, Folder 17)
  - Eggleston Rackcard 1194-002, 2009; Series 11 (Box 145, Folder 18)
  - Eggleston Press Preview 1194-013, 2009; Series 11 (Box 145, Folder 19)
  - Eggleston Contact Sheet 1194-012, 2009; Series 11 (Box 145, Folder 20)
  - Turnerr to Cezanne 1109-013, 2009; Series 11 (Box 145, Folder 21)
  - Financial Aid Postcard 1168-030, 2009; Series 11 (Box 145, Folder 22)
  - Financial Aid Reminder Postcard 1168-044, 2009; Series 11 (Box 145, Folder 23)
  - Fall 2009 Search Piece 1168-035, Series 11 (Box 145, Folder 24)
  - Undergrad Application 1168-005, 2009; Series 11 (Box 145, Folder 25)
  - Grad Open House Postcard 1241-004, 2009; Series 11 (Box 145, Folder 26)
  - Grad APplication 1241-003, 2009; Series 11 (Box 145, Folder 27)
  - Grad Inquiry Card 1241-001, 2009; Series 11 (Box 145, Folder 28)
  - Accepted Students Invite Fall '09 1168-030, 2009; Series 11 (Box 145, Folder 29)
  - Grad Enrollment Card 1241-02, 2009; Series 11 (Box 145, Folder 30)
  - CE Summer Promo Postcard/Ads 1242-019, 1239-033, 2009; Series 11 (Box 145, Folder 31)
  - Degrees Awards, 2009; Series 11 (Box 145, Folder 32)
  - New Program Announcement 1239-020, 2009; Series 11 (Box 145, Folder 33)
  - CE Postcard 124x-001, 2009; Series 11 (Box 145, Folder 34)
  - CE/Membership Card 1239-012, 2009; Series 11 (Box 145, Folder 35)
  - CE Spring 2010 Postcard 1246-014, 2009; Series 11 (Box 145, Folder 36)
  - 0809 Blank Admissions Postcard 1240-001, 2009; Series 11 (Box 145, Folder 37)
  - Open House Postcard 1168-039, 2009; Series 11 (Box 145, Folder 38)
  - Table Banner 1239-013, 1239-015, 2009; Series 11 (Box 145, Folder 39)
  - Enrollment FOrm 1240-009, 2009; Series 11 (Box 145, Folder 40)
  - MA Arts Ed. Brochure 1241-006, 2009; Series 11 (Box 145, Folder 41)
  - Housing Applicaiton, 2009; Series 11 (Box 145, Folder 42)
  - Undergrad Preview Postcard 1240-003, 2009; Series 11 (Box 145, Folder 43)
  - Application Waiver 1168-031, 2009; Series 11 (Box 145, Folder 44)
  - Member Info 1250-001, 2009; Series 11 (Box 145, Folder 45)
  - Membership Benefits 1187, 2009; Series 11 (Box 145, Folder 46)
  - Sargent Symposium 1228-002, 2009; Series 11 (Box 145, Folder 47)
  - Membership Collection 1187, 2009; Series 11 (Box 145, Folder 48)
  - Corocran Ball, 2009; Series 11 (Box 145, Folder 49)
  - Art Forum Luncheon Invitation 1250-004, 2009; Series 11 (Box 145, Folder 50)
  - Fall Fete Signage 1265-004, 2009; Series 11 (Box 145, Folder 51)
  - Donor Wall Plaques 1182-002, 2009; Series 11 (Box 145, Folder 52)
  - Comment Cards 1187-007, 2009; Series 11 (Box 145, Folder 53)
  - Learning Through Art 1256-001, 2009; Series 11 (Box 145, Folder 54)
  - Night and Day January 11520006, 2009 January; Series 11 (Box 145, Folder 55)
  - Night and Day October 1257-003, 2009 October; Series 11 (Box 145, Folder 56)
  - Fall Fete Invite 1265, 2009; Series 11 (Box 145, Folder 57)
  - Camp Creativity 1198, 2009; Series 11 (Box 145, Folder 58)
  - Family Day 1231, 2009; Series 11 (Box 145, Folder 59)
  - Avedon Teaching Packets 1195-001, 2009; Series 11 (Box 145, Folder 60)
  - Maya Lin Teachers Pack 1151-035, 2009; Series 11 (Box 145, Folder 61)
  - Artini 1203-003, 2009; Series 11 (Box 145, Folder 62)
  - 2009 Youth Family 1198-001, Series 11 (Box 145, Folder 63)
  - Corcoran Art Bar 1204-001, 2009; Series 11 (Box 145, Folder 64)
  - Eggleston Ads 1194, 2009; Series 11 (Box 145, Folder 65)
  - Power Hours 11899, 2009; Series 11 (Box 145, Folder 66)
  - Email Capuutre 1187-008, 2009; Series 11 (Box 145, Folder 67)
  - Maya Lin Ads, 2009; Series 11 (Box 145, Folder 68)
- Event files [legacy series], 1976-1983; Series 2
  This series contains correspondence and memorandum concerning the promotion of Gallery events, i.e. the Corcoran Ball.
  - Corcoran Ball, 1976 April 23; Series 2 (Box 161, Folder 6)
  - Corcoran Ball, 1976; Series 2 (Box 161, Folder 7)
  - Ball, 1977; Series 2 (Box 161, Folder 8-9)
  - Ball, 1978; Series 2 (Box 161, Folder 10)
  - Corcoran Ball, 1978; Series 2 (Box 161, Folder 11-12)
  - Corcoran Ball, 1979; Series 2 (Box 162, Folder 1)
  - Corcoran Ball, 1981; Series 2 (Box 162, Folder 2)
  - Corcoran Ball Photographs, 1982; Series 2 (Box 162, Folder 3)
  - Corcoran Ball, 1982; Series 2 (Box 162, Folder 4-5)
  - Corcoran Ball, 1983; Series 2 (Box 162, Folder 6)
- Event files, 1961-2007; Series 10
  This series contains records that detail the work of the Corcoran Gallery of Art public relations and graphics division of the Corcoran Gallery of Art. These records date primarily from 1961-2007.
  - FY '83 School Benefit 3rd Annual Affordable Art Auction, 1983; Series 10 (Box 20, Folder 1)
  - FY '84 School Benefit 4th Annual Affordable Art Auction, 1984; Series 10 (Box 20, Folder 2)
  - FY '85 School Benefit 5th Annual Affordable Art Auction, 1985; Series 10 (Box 20, Folder 3)
  - FY '86 School Benefit 6th Annual Affordable Art Auction, 1986; Series 10 (Box 20, Folder 4)
  - FY '84 29th Corcoran Ball Press Release, 1984; Series 10 (Box 20, Folder 5)
  - FY '84 29th Corcoran Ball Catalogue, 1984; Series 10 (Box 20, Folder 6)
  - FY '84 29th Corcoran Ball Guest List, 1984; Series 10 (Box 20, Folder 7)
  - FY '84 29th Corcoran Ball Fact Sheet, 1984; Series 10 (Box 20, Folder 8)
  - FY '84 29th Corcoran Ball Press Kits, 1984; Series 10 (Box 20, Folder 9)
  - FY '84 29th Corcoran Ball Seating Plan, 1984; Series 10 (Box 20, Folder 10)
  - FY '84 29th Corcoran Ball Committee Info, 1984; Series 10 (Box 20, Folder 11)
  - FY '84 29th Corcoran Ball Publicity and Clips, 1984; Series 10 (Box 20, Folder 12)
  - FY '86 31st Corcoran Ball Press Release, 1986; Series 10 (Box 20, Folder 13)
  - FY '86 31st Corcoran Ball Clips and Publicity, 1986; Series 10 (Box 20, Folder 14)
  - FY '86 31st Corcoran Ball VIP Guests, 1986; Series 10 (Box 20, Folder 15)
  - FY '86 31st Corcoran Ball Press Kits, 1986; Series 10 (Box 20, Folder 16)
  - FY '86 31st Corcoran Ball Catalogue, 1986; Series 10 (Box 20, Folder 17)
  - FY '87 32nd Corcoran Ball Press Release, 1987; Series 10 (Box 20, Folder 18)
  - FY '87 32nd Corcoran Ball Fact Sheet, 1987; Series 10 (Box 20, Folder 19)
  - FY '87 32nd Corcoran Ball Catalogue, 1987; Series 10 (Box 20, Folder 20)
  - FY '87 32nd Corcoran Ball Press Clips, 1987; Series 10 (Box 20, Folder 21)
  - FY '87 32nd Corcoran Ball Photo Info, 1987; Series 10 (Box 20, Folder 22)
  - FY '88 33rd Corcoran Ball Attendees, 1988; Series 10 (Box 20, Folder 23)
  - FY '88 33rd Corcoran Ball Press Kit, 1988; Series 10 (Box 20, Folder 24)
  - FY '88 33rd Corcoran Ball Press Announcement, 1988; Series 10 (Box 20, Folder 25)
  - FY '88 33rd Corcoran Ball Press Release, 1988; Series 10 (Box 20, Folder 26)
  - FY '88 33rd Corcoran Ball VIP Guest List, 1988; Series 10 (Box 20, Folder 27)
  - FY '88 33rd Corcoran Ball Invitation, 1988; Series 10 (Box 20, Folder 28)
  - FY '88 33rd Corcoran Ball Operations Schedule, 1988; Series 10 (Box 20, Folder 29)
  - FY '88 33rd Corcoran Ball Catalogue, 1988; Series 10 (Box 20, Folder 30)
  - [Washington Harbor Mural Press Release], 1984; Series 10 (Box 20, Folder 31)
  - FY '84 Washington Harbor Background, 1984; Series 10 (Box 20, Folder 32)
  - FY '84 Moulin Rouge Gala, 1984; Series 10 (Box 20, Folder 33)
  - FY '85 Challenge Grant - Press Release, 1985; Series 10 (Box 20, Folder 34)
  - FY '85 Gene Davis Memorial, 1985; Series 10 (Box 20, Folder 35)
  - FY '85 Gene Davis Press Release, 1985; Series 10 (Box 20, Folder 36)
  - FY '85 Millenium Concert Press Release, 1985; Series 10 (Box 20, Folder 37)
  - Corcoran School - Graduation Sr. Exhib., 1985 May; Series 10 (Box 20, Folder 38)
  - Corcoran School - Graduation Sr. Exhib., 1985 May; Series 10 (Box 20, Folder 39)
  - FY '86 FRIENDS 25th Anniversary Catalogue, 1986; Series 10 (Box 20, Folder 40)
  - FY '86 FRIENDS 25th Anniversary Press Kit, 1986; Series 10 (Box 20, Folder 41)
  - FY '86 FRIENDS 25th Anniversary Press Release, 1986; Series 10 (Box 20, Folder 42)
  - [FY '87 Wine Tasting Event], 1987; Series 10 (Box 20, Folder 43)
  - FY '87 Wine Tasting Event Fact Sheet, 1987; Series 10 (Box 20, Folder 44)
  - FY '87 Wine Tasting Event Press Announcement, 1987; Series 10 (Box 20, Folder 45)
  - FY '87 Wine Tasting Event Press Correspondence, 1987; Series 10 (Box 20, Folder 46)
  - FY '87 Wine Tasting Event Invitations, 1987; Series 10 (Box 20, Folder 47)
  - FY '88 Beaux Arts Masquerade Info, 1988; Series 10 (Box 20, Folder 48)
  - FY '88 Beaux Arts Press Release, 1988; Series 10 (Box 20, Folder 49)
  - FY '88 Beaux Arts PSA, 1988; Series 10 (Box 20, Folder 50)
  - FY '88 Beaux Arts Clips, Circa 1983-1988; Series 10 (Box 20, Folder 51)
  - FY '88 Beaux Arts Program Copy, 1988; Series 10 (Box 20, Folder 52)
  - FY '88 Beaux Arts Masquerade VIP List, 1988; Series 10 (Box 20, Folder 53)
  - FY '88 Beaux Arts Masquerade Fact Sheet, 1988; Series 10 (Box 20, Folder 54)
  - FY '88 Beaux Arts Masquerade Press Kits, 1988; Series 10 (Box 20, Folder 55)
  - FY '88 Berkowitz Memorial Service Clipping, 1988; Series 10 (Box 20, Folder 56)
  - FY '88 Berkowitz Memorial Service Press Release, 1988; Series 10 (Box 20, Folder 57)
  - [Easter Egg Roll and Wine Tasting Event], 1988; Series 10 (Box 20, Folder 58)
  - Corcoran Ball, 1962; Series 10 (Box 37, Folder 1)
  - Concerts, 1961; Series 10 (Box 37, Folder 2)
  - Memos and Letters About Concerts, 1962-1965; Series 10 (Box 37, Folder 3)
  - Art School, 1962-1962; Series 10 (Box 37, Folder 4)
  - Ceramics Department, 1962-1965; Series 10 (Box 37, Folder 5)
  - The Associates, 1962-1966; Series 10 (Box 37, Folder 6)
  - Loan of Corcoran Art To Embassies, 1963; Series 10 (Box 37, Folder 7)
  - Art School, 1964; Series 10 (Box 37, Folder 8)
  - Membership, 1964-1965; Series 10 (Box 37, Folder 9)
  - Art School, 1965; Series 10 (Box 37, Folder 10)
  - Corcoran Salutes Senators, Circa 1962-1980; Series 10 (Box 37, Folder 11)
  - Art School, 1966; Series 10 (Box 37, Folder 12)
  - New Acquisitions, 1966; Series 10 (Box 37, Folder 13)
  - Halpert, 1966; Series 10 (Box 37, Folder 14)
  - George Washington at Yorktown, 1966; Series 10 (Box 37, Folder 15)
  - Women's Committee House Tour, 1967 October; Series 10 (Box 37, Folder 16)
  - Women's Committee, 1967-1969; Series 10 (Box 37, Folder 17)
  - Art Rental Opening, 1967; Series 10 (Box 37, Folder 18)
  - Kreeger Tour, 1968; Series 10 (Box 37, Folder 19)
  - Sun Ra Performance, 1986 August 24; Series 10 (Box 37, Folder 20)
  - Consolidation CGA-WGMA, 1968; Series 10 (Box 37, Folder 21)
  - The Kinetic Art - Correspondence Advertsg., 1968; Series 10 (Box 37, Folder 22)
  - Membership, 1969; Series 10 (Box 37, Folder 23)
  - Corcoran Ball, 1969; Series 10 (Box 37, Folder 24)
  - Art Auction, 1969 December; Series 10 (Box 37, Folder 25)
  - Public Relations, 1969; Series 10 (Box 37, Folder 26)
  - Art School, 1969; Series 10 (Box 37, Folder 27)
  - Dupont Circle, 1969; Series 10 (Box 37, Folder 28)
  - Fairfax Sculpture 69 Project, 1969; Series 10 (Box 37, Folder 29)
  - CSA Lecture Courses, 1969; Series 10 (Box 37, Folder 30)
  - Concerts, 1969; Series 10 (Box 37, Folder 31)
  - Founder's Day, 1969; Series 10 (Box 37, Folder 32)
  - Concerts, 1970-1971; Series 10 (Box 37, Folder 33)